ซับไทยโดย Chuy Thai Fansub
facebook.com/ChuyFansub
ห้างสรรพสินค้า HaKaTa
นี่คือห้างไอดอล ที่ขายสินค้าอันทรงเสน่ห์ HKT48 สู่ตลาด
เหล่าลูกค้าแอนตี้ที่มาเยือนห้างซึ่งเติมเต็มด้วยสินค้าใหม่แห่งนี้
จะซื้อเมมเบอร์คนไหนกลับไปหรือไม่นะ?
อันเกิร์ลส์
ทานากะ ทาคุชิ
HKT48 ห้างสรรพสินค้า HaKaTa สาขาสาม!
ห้างฮากาตะสาขาสาม เริ่มต้นแล้วค่ะ!
วันนี้เราก็ต้อนรับศิลปินตลกชื่อดัง
ที่ไม่สนใจพวกเรา หรืออาจจะแอนตี้พวกเราอีกเช่นเดิมค่ะ
ทุกคนพยายามเข้านะ!
มาต้อนรับกันเลยค่ะ
สวัสดีคร้าบ
ทานากะ ทาคุชิซัง จากคู่หูอันเกิร์ลส์
ดูไม่ใช่แอนตี้เท่าไรเลยนะคะ
- ไม่เลยๆ
ดูชอบไอดอลจะตาย
ไม่ชอบซักหน่อย
เอ๋!? แต่ได้ข่าวว่า...
คุณชอบซายาเน่ไม่ใช่เหรอ?
- ใช่ๆๆ
เรื่องนั้นฉันไม่อยากเล่าเลยนะ
พยายามไม่เล่าอยู่
- ทำไมล่ะคะ?
มันน่าเกลียด
เอ๋!? ไม่น่าเกลียดเลยซักนิด
- ไม่น่าเกลียด?
ในฐานะคนชอบไอดอลเหมือนกัน เรื่องนั้นไม่เห็นน่าเกลียดเลยค่ะ
แต่หน้าตาคุณน่าเกลียด
แต่สรุปแล้วก็ชอบซายาเน่ใช่ไหมคะ?
ก็นะ ซายาเน่เขาน่ะ...
ร่างกายใช่มั้ย ร่างกาย
ไม่ได้ชอบที่ร่างกายซักหน่อย
ชอบร่างกายยามาโมโตะ ซายากะ
ชอบร่างกายแหงเลย
ฉันไม่ได้ดูที่ร่างกายซักนิด!
ไม่จริงๆ
- ไม่ใช่ๆๆ
ฉันชอบเธอจากหน้าตา แล้วถึงค้นพบร่างกายทีหลังต่างหาก!!
ค้นพบร่างกายในภายหลัง
ซายาเน่ไม่คิดว่าฉันน่าเกลียดน่ะ
ไม่มีใครคิดว่าน่าเกลียดซักหน่อยเนอะ?
ไม่คิดเลยๆ
เพิ่งบอกว่าน่าเกลียดเมื่อกี้เองนี่
แต่คุณเป็นคนอ่อนโยน ฉันชอบค่ะ
รู้แล้วเหรอว่าอ่อนโยน?
รู้สิคะ ก็คุณยิ้มตลอดเวลาไม่มีหุบเลย
ก็จริงนะ ยิ้มไม่หุบเลย
- ก็จริงนะ
เมื่อดูคำตอบของทานากะซังในแบบสอบถามเกี่ยวกับ HKT48...
เราถามมาแล้วค่ะว่าทำไมเขาถึงไม่สนใจ HKT48
นี่ค่ะ
เคยเจอแค่ซาชิฮาระซังคนเดียว
ไม่เห็นจะน่ารักอย่าง
ยามาโมโตะ ซายากะจังเลย
ใจร้ายที่สุด
นาโกะโกรธแล้วเนี่ย
ซาชิโกะเป็นโอชิเมมของนาโกะนี่นา น่ารักจริงๆ นะ
ไม่ๆ ไม่น่ารักเลย!
รสนิยม
ส่วนตัวชัดๆ
นิสัยเธอน่ะฉันให้ร้อยคะแนนเลย
ดูคนจากหน้าตานี่หว่า
เลือกไอดอลจากหน้าตามันแปลกตรงไหน!
งั้นแปลว่าฉันเข้าจอห์นนี่ส์ได้เหรอ?
ไม่ได้ใช่มั้ยล่ะ!?
สุดโต่งเกิน
ทานากะซังไม่คิดว่าฉันน่ารัก แล้วคิดยังไงกับคนอื่นๆ นี่ค่ะ
นี่ค่ะ
ลีดเดอร์ที่น่ารักที่สุดคือซาชิฮาระซัง
ดังนั้นคนอื่นๆ คงไม่น่ารัก
กว่าซาชิฮาระซังหรอก
โห่ร้องไม่พอใจกันใหญ่
อย่างงี้ได้ไง!
ก็ฉันไม่รู้จักนี่!!
จริงๆ นะ
การอัดเทปวันนี้
ต้องทำยังไงถึงจะหันมาสนใจ HKT48 ได้ เราถามมาแล้วค่ะ
นี่ค่ะ
ไม่พูดว่าผมน่าขยะแขยง
ไม่ขยะแขยงไม่ว่าจะโดนทำอะไร
นัตสึมิคัง
ยากนะ...
ทำยาก
อย่าพูดงั้นสิ
แต่ฉันชอบนะคะ
- เอ๋?
จริงเหรอ?
อ่านบล็อกด้วยค่ะ
เขียนบล็อกด้วยเหรอคะ?
ช่างเรื่องนั้นเหอะ
กลับกัน เมมเบอร์ HKT48 คิดยังไงกับทานากะซังกัน
มีคนที่ชมว่าเก่งในฐานะศิลปินตลกด้วยค่ะ
- เอ๋!?
ไม่ค่อยมีใครชมนะ
ใช่ค่ะ
อารามากิ มิซากิจัง
อารามากิ มิซากิ
อารามากิชอบทานากะซังตรงไหนกัน?
นี่ค่ะ
เลียนแบบท่าปูเก่ง
ไอ้ที่ทำประจำสินะ
ตลกเหรอ?
- ตลกค่ะ
อยากดูอะไรตลกๆ หน่อยค่ะ
อยากดู!!!
บอสเมินหน้าหนี
อยากให้ใครมาทำด้วยกันมั้ย?
คนที่อยากให้ทำด้วย...
ต้องเป็นคนที่แขนขายาว...
- บอส!
นัตสึมิคัง
ไม่เอาเด็ดขาด!!!
- นัตสึมิคังมานี่สิ
สมัยประถมน่ะ ฉันตัวสูงแถมยังผอมแห้ง
เลยโดนเรียกว่า อันเกิร์ลส์ทานากะ มาตลอดเลย!
ภาพสมัยอันเกิร์ลส์ทานากะ
ทำไมงั้น?
อ้อ ทานากะเหมือนกัน...
ทานากะ นัตสึมิ
ด้วยเหตุนี่ บอสที่นามสกุลเดียวกันจึงได้เป็นคนทำ
สุดยอด แขนขายาวมาก!
เหมาะเป็นปู
เหมาะกับการเป็นปูมากๆ
ปูชัดๆ เลย
แล้วก็ทำงี้
อย่างนี้?
- แล้วก็...
ทำท่าพร้อมขาแบบนี้
อย่างนี้
ไปเรื่อยๆ
เดินอย่างนี้
ปากเล็ก
ค่อยๆ กินๆ แบบปูน่ะ
คีบกิน แล้วก็ขยับอีกก้าว
ทำไปเรื่อยๆ
- สุดยอด!
ยอดๆ
ตัวเหมือนปูเลย
ตัวเหมือนปูค่ะ
เอาไปใช้ได้เลยนะ เต็มที่
- ไม่ต้องการค่ะ
จริงสิ โทโมนากะ มิโอะจังมีเรื่องอยากขอร้องทานากะซังค่ะ
ใช่ค่ะ
- อะไรรึ?
โทโมนากะ มิโอะ
คำขอร้องของโทโมนากะคือ?
เล่น "จังกะจังกะ" อยู่ประจำใช่ไหมคะ
เดี๋ยวนี้ไม่เล่นแล้ว
มัน...
- เมื่อหลายปีก่อนเล่นอยู่ประจำก็จริง
ภาพนั้นมันติดตามาก อยากให้โชว์ให้ดูวันนี้ค่ะ
แต่ยามาเนะไม่อยู่นี่นะ
จริงด้วย ต้องมีสองคนนี่นะ
- มีแต่ยามาเนะแหละที่รู้มุข
งั้นก็...
ให้เมมเบอร์ออกมาแทนได้ไหมคะ?
ก็ได้ แต่พวกเธอทำได้เหรอ กะทันหันงี้
- ใครอยากออกมาบ้าง?
ค่า
ทำไมมีแต่ฝั่งนี้...
ทำไมฝั่งนั้นไม่มีใครยกมือเลยเล่า
4/12 คน
ไม่เข้าใจว่าทำไมฝั่งนั้นไม่มีใครยกมือซักคน
- ฝั่งนี้คนชอบเยอะ
งั้นก็... นาโกะ!
เธอเหรอ?
- ให้คนที่อยากทำออกมาทำดีกว่า
งั้นก็... เอาไงดีนะ
ขอตกลงมุขก่อนได้มั้ย?
ได้ค่ะๆ เชิญเลย
ที่ไหนดี... นี่ละกัน
ยังกับโดนพาตัวไปที่ไหนซักแห่งเลย น่ากลัว!
- น่ากลัว!!
ไปดีมาดีนะ พยายามเข้า
- มามะๆ
ดังนั้น ยาบุกิจึงได้ตกลงเตรียมเล่นมุขตลกครั้งแรกในชีวิต
เชิญชมการแสดงของทั้งคู่ค่ะ
ตัวสูงต่างกันเกินไปมั้ย
สุดๆ
สูงไม่ถึงครึ่งเลยรึเปล่าเนี่ย
เชิญเล่น "จังกะจังกะ" ได้เลยค่ะ
ตลกสั้น ดึงผ้าปูโต๊ะ
เอ๋?
นาโกะจัง ดึงผ้าปูโต๊ะได้เหรอ?
ได้สิ
มีจานชามถ้วยโถวางอยู่ซะขนาดนี้นะ ได้จริงเหรอ?
สบายๆ ชิวๆ!
งั้นก็ทำให้ดูซิ
เอาล่ะนะ
โอ๊ยๆๆๆๆ
สุดยอด!
ไร้ที่ติ
สุดยอดเลย
เยี่ยม
กลับมาๆ
- เก่งมาก
นาโกะเล่นเก่งมากเลย
- เก่งๆ
กล้าดี เล่นเต็มที่ไม่มีเขินอายเลย
นาโกะ เป็นไงมั่ง?
สนุกมากค่ะ
เมื่อทานากะซังและ HKT48 เริ่มสนิทกันมากขึ้น
ก็มาดูเกมวันนี้กันดีกว่าค่ะ
ใส่ความรักไปพร้อมกับข้าว
เบ็นโตะกรังปรีซ์!
ทานากะซังเคยได้รับเบ็นโตะจากผู้หญิงมาบ้างไหมคะ?
ไม่เคย เคยแต่ได้จากแม่
จากคุณแม่คนเดียวเหรอคะ?
- ไม่เคยได้รับจากคนอื่นนะ...
จะได้เบ็นโตะจากผู้หญิง ต้องชวนไปออกเดทใช่มั้ยล่ะ
ทุกคนไม่ค่อยมีโอกาสจะทำเบ็นโตะให้ใครกินเนอะ?
ไม่มีประสบการณ์ที่โรงเรียนมั่งเหรอ? ทำให้คนที่ชอบอะไรงี้
ไม่มีๆ
ดังนั้น เมมเบอร์ HKT48 จะทำเบ็นโตะให้ทานากะซัง
มอบเป็นของขวัญ ครั้งแรกในชีวิตของพวกเธอเลย
เมมเบอร์ต่างทำเบ็นโตะด้วยไอเดียของตัวเอง
โดยหวังว่าทานากะซังจะชอบ
เป็นครั้งแรกเลยค่ะ ที่ฉันทำเบ็นโตะเพื่อให้คนอื่นทาน
อนึ่ง ในการให้คะแนน รสชาติไม่มีส่วนเกี่ยวข้องแม้แต่น้อย
ทานากะซังจะให้คะแนนจากหน้าตาที่ออกมา และคอนเซ็ปต์ค่ะ
เลือกสามอันดับแรกตามความชอบส่วนตัวล้วนๆ
เสร็จแล้ว
ดูใช้ได้เลย
เอาล่ะ นี่คือเบ็นโตะที่เมมเบอร์ต่างทำขึ้นมาค่ะ
กรุณาเลือกสามอันดับแรกจาก 12 กล่องที่เห็นนี้นะคะ
ทานากะซัง เชิญเลือกได้ตามสบายเลยค่ะ
ดูใกล้ๆ ได้เหรอครับ?
ค่ะ เชิญดูได้เลย
สโลแกน
เพื่อสุขภาพของเส้นผม!
แบล็กเบ็นโตะ
ราวคุณแม่
ทานากะซังทำเปี๊ยบ
เบ็นโตะรสฝีมือแม่
เบ็นโตะมีสโลแกนอธิบายคอนเซ็ปต์ของเมมเบอร์แต่ละคน
ความน่ารักเต็มร้อย!
ฮาร์ตเบ็นโตะ
แข็งแรงตลอดไป!
เบ็นโตะเปี่ยม
โปรตีนและไขมัน
จากลูกสาวสู่พ่อ
เบ็นโตะฟิตปึ๋งปั๋ง
แด่ทานากะซังที่งานยุ่ง
เบ็นโตะสู้ๆ นะ
ตอนนี้ซาชิฮาระและทานากะซังยังไม่รู้ว่าใครเป็นคนทำอันไหนค่ะ
รับรองผอมแต่กล้ามฟิต
เบ็นโตะสารอาหารครบ
แด่คุณโครงกระดูก
เบ็นโตะแคลอรี่สูง
ร่าเริง 99%!
เบ็นโตะของชอบทั้งนั้น
ลาก่อนผมบาง!
เบ็นโตะผมหนาปุกปุย
ข้างในมีอะไรต้องลุ้น!
เบ็นโตะรัสเซียนรูเล็ต
จากลูกสาวซึนเดเระ!
เบ็นโตะของขวัญวันพ่อ
ที่ฉันชอบน่ะนะ ก็พวกนี้
"พยายามเข้านะ" อะไรอย่างนี้
เห็นแล้วดีใจขึ้นมาเลย
If you saw this when you opened the box, it'd make you happy, right?
It's a cheering-you-on box lunch. "To the busy Tanaka-san."
This is my first time... It's something to be happy about. Really.
And this type, too.
Ah, it's cute.
Tanaka...
- Tanaka.
Di- Dive?
Double?
What is "Tanaka Double?"
Maybe they have the same last name?
Tanaka-san, maybe it's one of the Tanakas.
- Ah, it's one of the Tanakas.
One of them did it.
Ah, Double Tanaka. Like, eating together?
Eh?
To that extent?
Not to that extent.
Is this sakura denbu?
[T/N: Sakura denbu is mashed and seasoned fish that is a light pink color]
You don't like it that much?
- I don't really like it.
It doesn't really feel like a side dish.
And it's not something you put this much of.
That was one of the points.
Just then...
Hey, wait!
Isn't this...
Isn't this one a little too careless?
I didn't notice.
This looked quite good, but...
Riceball
Sweet & Sour Pork
Cherry Tomato
Lettuce
This is quite crude.
- It's crude.
The member who made that box lunch is...
I heard Tanaka-san likes sweet and sour pork.
This is my first time I made a box lunch.
Sakamoto Erena
Kenkyuusei
14 Years Old
Sakamoto Erena wasn't cutting corners. This was just her first time making a box lunch.
There's a really bad one. This one!
You cut corners! What is this?
You've got to be kidding me!
While thinking of ideas, she must have been like, "Tanaka-san is going bald, this would be good."
- That's right.
I'm not that concerned about going bald.
You're not concerned.
- What is this?
I wonder what this is...
Lasagna?!
This is lasagna with rice.
This is what Yamane likes.
Boss Makes a Basic Mistake
Yamane likes lasagna.
What is this?
Fresh cream and pistachios on top of pancake. I'm not sure why there's pistachio.
By the way, the cream on the pancake had made it onto the karaage chicken.
Because it's so messy.
Gross.
After briefly looking at all the box lunches, which one will Tanaka-san choose for 3rd place?
Say goodbye to thinning hair! Full head of hair box lunch.
It looks good!
If I'm being honest, I am a little concerned about my thinning hair. But she didn't emphasize it too much.
She's nice.
This amount of hijiki...
[T/N: A sea vegetable that's usually eaten with rice]
Inside my heart, this is about how much I care about going bald.
- Just a little. It's the perfect amount, right?
This is the perfect amount.
Who made this box lunch?
Me!
Wakachan!
It's Wakachan.
- That's good!
In 3rd place is Wakatabe Haruka.
The colors are all there. Yellow, red, green, everything is there.
- That's right.
I thought that maybe Tanaka-san was concerned about his thinning hair.
I searched for "thinning hair, food."
It came up with eggs and...
Is that so?
- Ah, eggs are good, too?
Hijiki and seaweed.
That's true!
Sautéed liver and Chinese chives, and inside here, there's natto and kimchi.
Woah, that's amazing!
Admirable!
It's good for baldness?
It's good for baldness.
In the end, this box lunch was all about my baldness.
Trying Really Hard to Counteract Baldness
- Yes.
But the fact that you didn't notice means she was able to do all that casually.
- I didn't notice. That's right.
Her casual kindness about his thinning hair was popular.
In 2nd place is...
With this, slim but muscular? Nourishing box lunch.
Whose box lunch is this?
Me!
Amazingly, Aramaki Misaki, a kenkyuusei, came in 2nd!
What was the main point?
This also has good colors. And the crab, that's a point.
- Ah, that's right. You like crab.
Good on you for thinking about the distribution. Did you also think about the colors?
Yes.
That's good. You're really...
You're a really good kid.
- How is it?
Do you think you did well?
Hmm, putting them into the box was hard.
It was hard?
What's your favorite part of this?
Of course the crab.
Ah, it's the crab. Because he likes crab, right?
- Ah, that's right.
I want him to turn completely into a crab and then eat this crab.
Fixating on Tanaka-san's special talent of turning into a crab, she amazingly comes in 2nd.
Who will come in 1st?
1st place is...
For the busy Tanaka-san! Cheering-you-on box lunch!
Whose box lunch is this?
Me!
Ah, Aoi!
Congrats!
Coming in 1st is Motomura Aoi.
Opening this in the dressing room would certainly be embarrassing.
- True.
I don't know what Yamane would say to me if he saw this.
But a man wants someone to make him something like this at least once.
The kind that makes you say, "This is a little embarrassing!" while eating it.
Like the "Stop it!" one.
I wouldn't want this every time, but if I opened this up when I was tired,
it'd make me think, "I need to keep working hard."
"I need to keep working hard for Motomura-chan."
Ah, she's delighted.
- I'm happy!
A heart-shaped omurice with an egg on top of chicken rice.
Although nervous about how this is a one time deal, Motomura writes a message.
I did it!
Thanks and congrats.
- The best, the best.
1st place.
- Yay for you.
Congrats.
- Thank you very much.
Tashima Meru
Kojina Yui
Even though the judging is finished, there is one box lunch Tanaka-san wants to complain about.
Yabuki Nako
Moriyasu Madoka
I'm curious about this!
Who?
Me!
You've got to be kidding me, seriously.
- Mio!
What the hell is this?
- Please don't get mad! Wait, please listen to me.
Tell me how things got this way.
Um.
You know how you're thin?
- I'm thin.
That worries me, so
I thought giving you high-calorie foods would help bulk you up, which would make you look better.
A pancake with plenty of fresh cream on top.
And katsudon, karaage chicken, and even sweet and sour pork since you love it.
- Sweet and sour pork is too heavy!
Let me rest my stomach!
Since it seems he's in a bad mood, they propose this idea...
You'll feed one dish from your box lunch to Tanaka-san.
- Eh?!
Ah.
You're kinda against it.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Being fed is definitely one of the things men yearn for.
Plus, this is the box lunch you made for Tanaka-san.
- That's true.
Except, you're going to feed me this?
This
That's right.
- Why?
But the other ones are quite bad, too.
Maybe you should feed him some other stuff, too.
The shell.
- Hold on.
How about the shell?
Can you eat it with the shell on?
Of course I can't eat it!
I'm not a monster!!
Why would I eat the shell?
Then Tanaka-san, please eat.
Ok! Open wide!
Wah.
Don't say "wah."
How is it?
It's surprisingly good.
I'm glad!
I'm happy. I'm glad.
Let's play with Tanaka-san! Daruma-san's Day!
[T/N: Daruma-san's Day is a children's game that is sort of like a combination of "Red Light, Green Light" and "Simon Says"]
Ok, from now, in order to become more familiar with Tanaka-san, we'll have him play with us.
We want to play Daruma-san's Day today.
Do you know what that is?
I don't know.
- Eh?! You don't know it?!
Who knows what Daruma-san's Day is?
Common Knowledge for Teenagers
Everyone knows it?
The rules are almost the same as Red Light, Green Light.
However, the participants must do whatever the person acting as "it" says.
So if "it" says, "I ate ramen," you have to pretend to eat ramen.
I see.
You have to do the movements properly.
Ok.
The "it" is Tanaka Miku, who was in elementary school until last year.
The first action is...
Daruma-san turned into Tanaka-san!
As expected, Tanaka-san is the best at that.
He's good! Can you do it?
It's like, "Yamane!"
- Ah, that's it!
Everyone, do it!
- Why couldn't you guys get that?
Everyone, do it! Yamane.
Yamane!
No, you have to do more. Yamane!
Meru, were you able to do it?
Yamane...
No, no, your voice is too soft.
Yamane!
If you don't do that much, Yamane won't stop.
Right, right.
Afterwards, Daruma-san turned into a gorilla.
What is this?
Fell in love.
Fell in love and...
I've come to like you.
Tanaka-san, when you fall in love, you turn into that?
You turn into that!
What will Daruma-san do next?
Daruma-san tripped.
Tripped?
You're good!
Everyone's good, as expected.
They're good at falling.
- It looks like it hurts. Like he broke a bone.
The important part is what you do afterwards.
You have to continue acting.
Continue acting.
Continue acting until there's a cut.
Haruppi, does it hurt?
It hurts! I broke something.
You broke something? Are you ok?
I'm not ok.
This "suu suu" noise you make is important.
- Suu suu?
Suu--
Don't all do it!
And then, in the end...
Daruma-san went bald.
Everyone, go bald.
Like that, like that. Nako!
Manly, manly.
She's balding too much.
Pull it back more!
Incredible.
If you do that, no one will tease me about going bald.
If you do it like that.
Ok Tanaka-san, how was your shopping experience today?
Well, it was fun.
It was fun? Yay!
It's not often that I get to have a good time with women like this.
- That's true.
It was practice for talking to women.
Ah, that's good. Did everyone have fun?
It was fun!
Finally, Ungirls Tanaka-san will announce his oshimen.
I...
Tanaka,
have decided that my HKT48 oshimen is...
It's Tomonaga-chan!
Eh, no way!
It's because you made the box lunch that left a big impression.
It was my first time being fed by a woman.
Your first time?
As the first woman.
How do you feel? Are you happy?
Honestly Puzzled
Yes, I'm happy. Very much so.
- You're happy about it?
You just wanted the badge at all costs.
You can't lose it here.
Tomonaga, who was chosen as Tanaka-san's oshimen, will receive a gourmet reward after this.
There's a reason these two are the MCs this week.
Let's think of a chara for MC Aramaki!
Aramaki Misaki
Tanaka Natsumi
So suddenly!
On today's Annex, it was decided that they will make kenkyuusei Aramaki cosplay.
We'll discuss what we want Aramaki-chan to wear.
Me!
Yes, Haruppi.
Something white and fluffy. Kind of angel-like.
I see.
Then, Moripo.
Eh? What could it be...
Maybe a devil.
I feel like she'll turn into a small devil.
That's right. If she were a devil, it'll be completely fine.
- I'll be ok with her doing anything to me.
Right?
When we look at the HKT members' questionnaire...
From Matsuoka Natsumi-chan...
Wearing [censored], I want her to hold a stuffed animal.
Therefore, using the questionnaire answers as reference, Boss decides on the cosplay outfit.
What kind of outfit will she come out wearing?
Misaki-chan!
Yes.
Cute!
What Kind of Cosplay Will Aramaki Come Out Wearing?
Misaki-chan!
Yes.
Cute!
White Pajamas
+ A Bunny Stuffed Animal
Cute!
Better than I imagined!
There's something I want you to say.
I want her to be frank and say, "Oniichan, I love you."
Yes.
Then, please!
Oniichan, I love you!
Cute!
I'll be your oniichan!
Eh? You can't become that!
A must-see for fans!
The complete Aramaki MC episode will be available exclusively on Hulu!
Umm...
Do your best!
- Can you do it?
It's ok.
I'm not sure who the host is supposed to be.
HaKaTa Hyakkaten 3 will still continue after this!
I won't let you fall asleep.
Today's gourmet reward is from Garrett Popcorn Shop. It's the Chicago mix,
2 gallon can!
This is cool!
- Amazing!
What is this?
- Looks delicious!
You're supposed to eat this together.
Is that so?
- It's really pretty.
That's right.
Looks delicious. Please try it, Mio-chan.
Then, itadakimasu.
I'm going to eat 2.
- Looks delicious!
How is it?
- It's delicious.
It's good?
How is it different from the one you eat at the movie theater?
As expected, it's completely different.
- It's completely different?
There's the sweet one, and the spicy one is on this side.
Ah, the salty one is on this side.
It's a good mix.
I see.
Then let's eat.
- Let's eat.
Please eat.
Wah, it's a crab.
You're right...
That's disgusting!
She already received the badge, so she's like this now.
That's disgusting.
Not good anymore.
Don't say that!
You've got to be kidding me, seriously.
Next week, they will welcome Shisonnu and do a monoboke competition.
That's good.
After this, a word from the members that will perk you up.
ซับไทยโดย Chuy Thai Fansub
facebook.com/ChuyFansub
An announcement from the show.
HaKaTa Hyakkaten 3 will be available on Hulu and NTV on-demand.
For more information, head to the show's homepage.
Moriyasu Madoka
I'll do my best to talk more. Please cheer me on.